Dry Garlic with Ginger Ale
Thank you for watching.
See you soon.
Mmm
mmm
ahhhhh ahhh ahhh ahhh ahhh ahhh ahhh ahhh ahhh ahhh ahhh ahhh ahhh ahhh
good night!
I can't do it, I haven't done it in years.
I've been to the festival for the first time in months, maybe three times on the third day.
I'm sure you'll be able to find a way to get a souvenir of this that you mentioned to me right away.
What's with the spring colors?
Thank you very much for the gift!
I heard you didn't start the kizar collar.
What did you do today?
I'm going to be on youtube with Gorgeous and Honoka today to do a live performance.
I was given a video of me winning Epic Dog.
I've been watching it a lot, and people think I'm dancing too much, so I've been taking it all in.
Yeah, yeah, yeah...
ni
That's the side song.
This video is brought to you by Nukumeshi who eats rice with Nukumeshi
I'm looking forward to it.
They have drinks and food. They have delicious meat.
I'm so happy.
Why the salt?
What do you want?
Roast beef on rice, stew, or beef tenderloin on rice?
I'm not sure what I'm going to have for lunch today, but I'm going to have lunch at the Nix Grill, which is like an eight-mix grill, with chicken for the crowd.
And the beef?
I haven't had Gan Chikyu yet, right?
I'll have a big shin on this one.
I'll have a Coke at Carla's.
Yes, now.
Two roast beef bowls, a Coke, and a regular ginger ale.
Thank you.
I think we have some dry ginger, too.
You like it?
I do.
Oh, really?
I like it spicy.
I don't drink much.
I don't think I drink much.
I like the way it leaves a tingling sensation.
Yes, I'm used to sweet.
I'm used to sweet.
You said you're used to it.
That's cute.
I'm used to the sweet taste.
We've never even met in private.
That's right.
It's the first time, right?
It's the very first time.
I'm glad.
I've always just had this image of you in costume.
He does, too, so...
It's refreshing to see you in plain clothes.
Really?
Haru asked me about it today.
As I noticed.
Isn't she too cute?
Thank you so much.
If you can't make it to the Stab fest...
It's been three months or so.
We're doing an event together in Fukuoka on February 4th.
I know this is before that.
That's right.
Do we both have birthdays?
Yes, we did.
Probably.
We'll be older the next time we see each other.
That's right.
What do we do now?
What do we do?
What do you want to do?
How old will you be next time?
Twenty-five.
25, so you're in Alaska.
No, I'm not in Alaska because I'm an idol.
No, I won't be.
Ha ha ha ha
You're beautiful.
I wonder if I'll make it.
Chansa 22?
I'll be 22.
I remember how happy I was.
I'll be 22 on the 2nd of February.
That's right.
We'll be together, right?
That's right, isn't it?
Aren't you happy?
Of course I'm happy.
That's because it's starting.
When you pick a lucky number, you tend to pick two.
I know.
That's right.
By all means, let's go with "kyan-yan.
NyanNyan, please.
I want you to give me a picture of NyanNyan on my birthday.
Let's take a picture together next time.
Let's take a picture together.
Nyan Nyan
Yes, of course.
Yes, you're right.
Even if our birthdays are different, if we have the same birthday, we might share the same star sign.
I'd like to look for commonalities today.
I'd like to look for commonalities, and on the other hand, we have the same birthday, but our personalities are totally different.
Yes, that's possible. Their personalities are totally different. They do seem different.
What's it like? What's it like? What's it like?
But Chan-set must be really healed.
Every time I see her at the festival, she's so cute... all the girls from StarPlaza are so cute.
I'm just trying to traffic the pictures, and I'm going back and forth with the camera, and the camera, and the camera, and the camera, and all these people booing and booing.
Chancetta is the only one taking pictures.
It's true that you take pictures every time.
That's right.
I'm really sorry for the fans.
I'm sorry for the fans.
You know how we all take selfies together?
Like, let's take a picture together.
That's right.
Chancetta is so cute next to me when we take pictures.
She usually takes pictures with Haru's cell phone.
She took a picture of me before and posted it on twitter or something.
That's right, that's right.
I put it up!
I'm so glad!
It's so cute!
And he was a fox.
Yes, he was so cute.
It looked really good on you.
Thank you.
I'm so glad. But I guess I'm Haru-chan's image.
I wonder.
When did you first meet her? The first time we met...
Maybe before the battenshon itself.
We had a chance to say hello, but we didn't have a chance to talk.
But we didn't have a chance to really talk until after the battement itself.
I think it was after a while since we started the battement itself.
I was wearing a "Yes, that's right" T-shirt, and I remember the T-shirt.
I remember the T-shirts from Fukuoka.
I remember.
I wonder how long ago it was.
Our group is celebrating our 9th anniversary this year, so it's been 9 years, almost 10 years.
It's been almost 10 years.
I'm surprised it's been that long.
I don't know how long it's been.
I've always felt like an older sister to you because of the passage of time.
I still feel like an older sister, but I feel comfortable with it.
Smiling.
I see your face all the time.
You don't have eyes.
You nod.
It's true that Basho is a little bit like a sister to Orca.
She's like a direct sister to Orca.
If it's Ebichu-chan, she's not like Misa Sakurai and now she's somewhere else, but maybe that's how she feels.
They're from different parts of Japan.
They also do Moo Snacks and Rhythm.
I wonder if she's really my sister.
I don't know, but...
I don't know...
Earth cutoff all lights strangers
I'm not sure if it's a sister or not.
Doron, I think it's a Sasquatchism.
I think it's the same blood that's been flowing in our veins since we started to develop our localism.
The first thing that comes to mind is the fact that the two groups are related, especially the three of them.
Tako-chan used to be there too.
There's something about the way we all fit in, isn't there?
They're all kind of loose, aren't they? Yes, they are loose, but there's a gap between them and the stage.
Sorry for the wait. Here they are. Thank you.
Thank you very much. Thank you very much. Next, please bring the linkers.
Thank you very much. - It's delicious. It's glowing.
There you go. - It's good.
It's glowing. It's glowing, isn't it?
Thank you very much.
It's a very nice meat, isn't it?
Yes, it is.
Matsuzaka beef.
Matsuzaka beef. Toboggan.
Very, very good!
So shiny!
This is the meat of the buttocks, called ichibo.
It's so tender!
Thank you very much.
So you've lost weight.
Is that okay?
Take it, take it, take it, take it.
So cute!
I wonder if he's going to be over here like this already, together today.
I'll take a picture of you, too.
Oh, you're going to take my picture? I'm so glad.
Here we go. Here we go.
Here we go. I'm going to take a close-up of the maid.
Here you go, cheese.
I'll do this one too. Here we go.
So cute.
Can we take a picture with them too?
All of you?
Let's take a picture together.
Cute.
Okay, I'll go for you.
Yes, I'm coming for you.
Mmm! It looks good!
Thank you!
Send it to me later.
I'll send it to you.
It's really beautiful.
It's amazing.
Amazing.
This is amazing.
I've never had a roast beef bowl before.
I know what you mean.
I'm with you.
But I have this image of a girls' night out.
Of course.
I thought it looked like a girls' night out.
To the February 2nd birthday party.
Cheers!
That's great.
The soda's really kicking in, isn't it?
I'm glad.
Looks delicious.
I've never had dinner with my juniors like this.
Everyone in StarPlaza...
We've talked about going out for dinner.
But the people in the local area, or the people in the local rhythm...
That's right.
I wonder how they eat.
I wonder if they put it on.
I think so.
Shall we put it on?
I'll pour it on.
Here we go.
There it is!
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
It smells good.
I'll put condiments on it later.
I'll do that.
Bon appétit.
Are you finished?
What do you usually do? Do you crack an egg or something first?
I eat half normally, and half a little thicker.
Spring is the same.
I think I save the eggs until the end, even if they're in the noodles.
That's right.
So, let's start with a piece and eat it boldly.
That's true. If you eat only the meat.
It's really good.
Bon appétit.
Mmm.
Mnh-mnh.
Oh, no.
Uh-uh.
It's gone.
No more.
Delicious!
This is Tokyo Roast Vegan
This is Tokyo? I felt Tokyo.
This is delicious. It's the best.
It's really delicious.
The meat itself is cut a little thin,
But it's also very chewy,
Thank you for the 100 point report.
It's really tender, really tender. It's gone in the blink of an eye.
It seems to disappear in an instant.
It's hard work.
The egg broke.
It happens, doesn't it?
It does happen, doesn't it? I'm going to put it on now.
It's the best.
Wow! It goes well with rice!
I can't get enough of it. It's so good. Do you go out to eat with other members? With the STAPLER members?
Yes, I do. Really? Did you go out with Miyazaki once? Yes, I had plans with Miyazaki once, and he accompanied me to a curry restaurant.
That's right. I've been to Fukuoka once, but other than that, I've rarely been to Fukuoka. I have been to Tokyo before, but I have rarely been to other places.
And when I am in Tokyo, I have to do a lot of work in Tokyo. When I am in Tokyo, I have to work hard in Tokyo. That's right. I don't know what time I finish at night, so it's not that easy.
I don't know what time they finish at night, so it's not so easy. You can't go out. I don't go out for dinner at night, but I would like to. With a lot of people. Yes, that's true.
It's just, you know, it's in the countryside. But isn't it springtime? Tokyo is pretty much the same. Yes.
Depending on the month, sometimes there are more people in Tokyo and sometimes more people in Nagoya, and sometimes it's about 50-50, but it's not that common.
That's right. I am really glad. Thank you very much. Thank you for inviting me. I'm really happy.
It's a birthday party. Just the two of us. It's true. I think we could do it in Fukuoka, too. That's for sure. A birthday party for just the two of us.
Wow. Then let's make it just the two of us.
Two people are two years old? That's right. But, you know, you're pretty and you've got money, but you're also beautiful, so you're like a big sister to me.
Really? Yes. In a beautiful way.
Oh, my, oh, my. Is that why things are changing? I'm going to be more extreme than a beautiful woman.
If you say so, I'll do my best.
Mmm-hmm.
But, Haru, you may have been the youngest, but I didn't feel that way at all,
I always thought of you as more like an older sister,
I always thought of you as more like an older sister, and even now you're still the same kind of older sister.
I'm glad to hear that.
I'll try it.
Thank you very much.
Yes, thank you very much.
Maybe the staff, or even people who have just met you for that matter, will tell you.
They might tell me that I'm lower than them, so I might be looked at that way a lot.
But how long has it been since you two joined as new members?
It has been three years.
Lil' Mille is cute.
I was going to say many things, but she is really cute.
She's really cute.
I think she's really cute.
Including everything. Of course, her face is cute,
And of course her face is cute, and her atmosphere is cute,
Her personality is really cute.
Even if the members see it, it's really cute.
I always think of her as precious and wonder if it would be okay for me to be in the dressing room,
But there was always an atmosphere of Batention itself,
When we decided to bring in a new member,
But when we decided to bring in a new member, he or she seemed to be a very trendy kid.
If I had seen that, I would have thought, "What am I going to do?
I'm curious about that, but the reason we decided to bring in a new member was because...,
There were various proposals.
I wonder if that was discussed by everyone.
A member decided to quit,
How about having the remaining four members and the four older members? We discussed it,
Maybe we could bring in a new member and give a breath of fresh air to the group,
I thought it might be a good idea to bring in a new member and give a new wind to the group.
Including the songs that Nukeso has written in the past,
I also felt that four members would not be enough,
The image of six members was stronger for us,
So the staff and our manager at the time and I came to a consensus,
The staff, the manager at the time, and the members of the group all agreed,
Everyone was in agreement.
That's right.
But we didn't know what kind of girls we were going to get,
There were a lot of them, but I didn't know them very well,
But I had a chance to attend Ai-chan's birthday party, and some of the students from my lessons were going to be there,
At that time, I was really impressed with Lil Mille,
I thought they were both amazing. Did some of them perform?
Yes, they were. They were all so cute, danced well, and sang really well,
I was really impressed and thought we couldn't do something like this in the past,
I thought the level was really high, but Lil Miyu stood out among them,
That's right. I thought they were already idols.
I was impressed. At that point.
That's right. Her singing is also amazing.
Miyu sings especially well and dances beautifully.
She used to be a ballet dancer, so she is beautiful.
That's right.
Lira-chan has never sung before,
She had never sung before, but she used to dance as a cheerleader,
Is it because everyone else was doing it?
Yes, that's right. That's right.
The "ping-pong" is really an idol! I feel like this is what you are looking for.
It really is. She is a natural-born idol.
She really is like a rabbit.
Really.
I can see that. It looks like he has ears.
It really does.
Yes, it does.
But from then on, I was thinking that these two were great,
The manager and Ai-chan recommended them to me,
I thought it would be a good idea, and I thought they would fit the atmosphere of the place,
But I didn't know their personalities, so we hadn't talked much.
I've only seen them in faformances.
That's right. So, I'm very serious, and I'll say something like, "Oh, my God, I'm so sorry," or something like that.
When the gals come.
That's right.
If she's like, "How are you doing, senpai? What should I do if it's a girl like that?
That's right. I think that kind of girl would be fine,
But that version would be very interesting.
It would be complicated and surprising for the members at first.
Yes, that's right. I thought it was interesting, too,
But there is an element of uneasiness.
That's right. But when I met them, I realized that even their personalities are excerpted.
That's amazing. Do you remember the first time we met? Then.
I remember.
I remember how he greeted me so clearly,
I felt that he was willing to do his best in everything.
Oh, that's right.
I was also impressed by the way both of them learned the choreography for several songs in a day,
Maybe there are new members in other groups, too.
But, you know, the amount of things you have to memorize is huge because of the distance between the two of you.
Yes, that's right.
It's amazing, isn't it? We are all on the same team.
Haru and the others are not new members, so I don't know,
I don't know, but it's amazing. The amount of things you have to learn.
Yes, it is. I really don't think I would be able to do the amount of work I have to do,
I am very grateful that they worked so hard while going to school.
I also have a feeling of gratitude.
It's amazing.
I'm sure they will become idols that many fans will support,
I'm kind of excited.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
It makes us feel that we have to work harder, and we certainly feel a new wind.
Yes, I do. I really feel it.
Recently, we felt like we had to do our best because we were the junior members,
But now, I feel more and more that I have to leave it to Lil Mille.
I see. That's great. That's great. I feel like I've grown a lot.
I really feel like I'm growing in many areas, and I feel like I'm going to work harder and harder.
That's great.
Seeing Lil Mille makes me want to work hard too.
That's nice. That's a nice story.
I'm in a bit of trouble. I haven't been able to eat. I can't talk at all.
I'm not kidding.
I'm looking forward to it.
In the midst of eating.
It's fun, isn't it? Talking while eating.
It's fun, isn't it?
Let's eat.
I really liked them, and I thought that they both had something amazing in common, and as a viewer, I thought that they matched Nukoso's good color very well.
Even the members talked about it a lot.
Really?
I can feel it. I can feel it.
I'm happy too. I don't know.
Yeah. That's how far you've grown.
Really.
Yeah, yeah.
Thanks to Lil Mille.
Are you watching now? Lil' Mille.
Hey, are you watching?
I want you to watch.
I want you to watch me.
It's good.
It's delicious.
You're a good eater, aren't you?
Mmm-hmm.
I have that impression. Wasn't there some kind of food title? That's right. From Kyushu.
I can't say the word, but it's perfect.
The catchphrase?
I'm the president of the Kyushu Food Culture Lovers Association, and since I love to eat, I thought it would be great if I could promote Kyushu's delicious food.
That's great.
It's great, isn't it? I mean, you can only get this warm feeling in Nagoya, Aichi, or in other regions of Japan.
That's right.
But I think it would be different in Kanto or Tokyo. Especially Shachi-chan's songs are full of love for Nagoya.
Really?
Indeed. In the songs.
So, as a local group, we are using Shachi's songs, performances, and love for Nagoya as a great reference, or rather, as a reference,
Really?
Yes, that's right.
Of course, it's the experience of sightseeing.
Yes, of course.
Well, now that we know so much about Nagoya, we want to introduce and promote Nagoya with a strong love for it.
Yes.
Yes, I see.
I see.
Yes.
Yes, I see.
I used to live in Nagoya.
I used to live in Nagoya. Yes, that's right.
I lived in Kariya City for only one year.
I was in elementary school. What? This is the first time I've heard that information.
I was in elementary school when I heard that information for the first time.
I was there at the time, so I feel like my taste buds are tinted
When we say "miso", we mean "aka miso" here
That's probably why... when I drink aka-miso miso soup, I feel at ease.
It's like when you drink aka-miso miso soup, you feel at ease
I can see why.
If you ask me which one is better, I'll definitely choose the red one first if they have both at the store.
I'm glad. What kind of miso is the soup?
I guess it's more like a combination of the two.
Did you put miso on oden? I haven't had oden that often in the past year.
Yes, but I like to put miso on tofu and put miso on tofu and put miso on tofu and put miso on tofu and put miso on tofu and put miso on tofu and put miso on hot fries.
I remember that I liked to put it on hot deep-fried tofu, or fried tofu, or even rice.
There's a theory that dipping miso in soy sauce is the strongest, so it must be the strongest.
There's always a tube of mayonnaise in the fridge.
Miso miso, put miso on top of miso
That's cute.
That's right.
Miso is a must for oden (Japanese stew).
But there are people who don't understand how delicious it is.
I sometimes have arguments with the manager about people who haven't experienced it.
Like, "I'm sure it's miso, but this oden is delicious too," and they fight because they won't eat it without miso.
We fight with each other because we won't eat without miso.
By the way, Nukasa was in the camp of bringing in new members.
But Shachi-chan has never brought in a new member, right?
No, we haven't.
That's right.
So I was wondering why that is, or rather, what it was like, and I wonder if I may ask you...
We don't talk about this kind of thing.
But Orca started with 6 members and then they started with 5 and then 4.
It's not like we don't talk about it when we graduate.
I see.
I heard there was an idea like that.
We did, but some of the members were in favor of it or didn't want me to be in it.
Mm-hm.
And then we split up, and the manager respected that opinion, and we became the final members.
We had a lot of discussions even after the group was formed.
I know that the word "discussion" gives a stiff image, but there was a phase where we had meetings and talked about everything with the members and the staff.
That's right.
We do a lot of talking at that time.
Yes, that's right.
We couldn't say anything even at this point, so we decided to go as far as we could with just the four of us, so we haven't included it yet.
I see.
But it's true that the atmosphere at Shachi-chan, or the bond between the group members, is very strong.
That makes me happy.
That's why I'm glad.
I thought that I would like to participate in this end of Arena Haratatsu and this gymnastics ath from Korone's 2021 book.
I mean...
Yeah.
When I think about it, it's a game.
Final!
I'm not dunking anymore today Crime
el empez h iconic
After that
Äaug können
Yes كر 막
yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, mes english amazing the song you can watch together and sing away, something that holds a lot of who the power with the damage carbon bonding object that increase it to the overall night.
But, I guess when you work with the same members for a long time, you tend to get spoiled by each other,
I think we need a new style,
But I also thought to myself, which is what is required of us?
I chose not to include them,
So if we don't stimulate each other, we will become accustomed to each other,
That's why we always try to keep our originality in mind at our recent live performances,
So, we are always conscious of saying things like, "Don't forget your first love," to the manager and the rest of the team.
I see. That's right.
That's great.
I don't know how much,
But I can see how you might take advantage of the team members,
Don't you think so? The longer you work with them, the more you feel spoiled.
But I think that's very important.
It's also a good thing for the team.
If there is a child who is good at something, it is better to ask that child to do it.
If there is a girl who is good at what she does, she will shine, and the people around her will think she is better suited for the position, right?
Yes, that's true.
That's why not everyone can do it,
I think that is the difficult part of a team.
That's right.
Everyone in Nukoso is a completely different type of person,
So, we are all different types, and some of us pursue what is best suited for each type,
We leave things to each other,
But with Shachi-chan, I feel that everyone is capable.
For example, when they talk, they all talk at the same time, and they talk and talk and talk.
When I see that, I feel that the atmosphere, the way of doing things, and the way of thinking are a little different from Nukeso's. I wanted to know more,
I wanted to know more about it.
Really?
On the other hand, the good thing about our group is that we leave the talking to the other members like Shio-chan,
For a while, the four members of Shachi also had their own talk shows, just like you just said,
As the four of us got used to it, we were able to do more and more things, and when everyone was able to do them,
I think that the position of the group is not good if everyone talks too much.
Oh, yes.
That's true.
There were moments when I felt that it was difficult.
Yes, yes. I understand.
I understand.
I understand. I understand that.
Everyone can do it, but there is something about having a good member who is out of the loop,
Depending on the place or situation, you may learn that such looseness is necessary.
Yes, there is.
You are talking a lot, Shachi-chan.
Yes, I think so.
Are there things you are careful about in connecting with others, or are there things you would like to do in this way?
But, like now, when we talked...,
I don't know.
But, like now, when we talk about it...well...we don't produce the other members, but the three of us..,
For example, if it's Yuzuki, then Yuzuki is really Yuzuki,
Yuzuki, for example.
Yuzuki, for example, would say something funny or something out of the ordinary, and not only Yuzuki,
Sometimes his words are a little weak, or he has a weak feeling,
Yeah, yeah.
And Hou-chan and Naoto also have their own points of view, like they are a little loose today,
But Hou-chan and you both have your own loose ends to pick up on, and you both sense it, and you both know that you're the one for the day,
Ah, yes.
We can sense each other's feelings even if we don't say it to each other.
I see.
That's right.
So, I think that orcas are not easy to be bullied, or easy-to-understand bullied characters,
I guess so.
Maybe it depends on the day.
Yes, that's right.
That's right.
Yes.
I have an image of that,
Do you have that image?
Yes, I do.
I don't know if he will ever be a blur,
Yes, yes.
Everyone is kind of disjointed, but they are all talking at the same time,
It's interesting to watch.
So it was interesting to watch.
It's fun.
That's right.
Yeah, yeah.
I'm glad. But that's not enough time at all.
It's really not enough. I want to talk for about four more hours.
I'm sure we can make it.
I want to do karaoke.
You want to do karaoke, too.
Yes, I do.
Heh. Shall we go?
Let's go.
Really, let's go.
I have often just said, "I want to go," and that was the end of it, so I really want to go in 2024.
Let's go.
Let's make it our goal.
Let's make it our goal. Let's go right away.
Yes, let's go. If you say you will come to Tokyo or go to Nagoya, then...,
Well, to begin with, will you make a phone comment?
I'll make a phone comment.
Let's do it.
Yes, I will.
Then, do you have a chance to come to Nagoya?
Oh, yes. Just.
Just.
Just in time. Do you know the dates?
Well, we're going on a ZEPP tour in March and April, Fukuoka and Tokyo.
Tokyo?
Yes, there will be a tour in Fukuoka, Tokyo, Osaka, and Nagoya. Fukuoka, Tokyo, Osaka, and Nagoya.
You are in Nagoya.
This is Nagoya's chance, isn't it?
It's in March. I wish I could go.
I wish I could go.
That's right.
It's been a while since I've been on the ZEPP tour.
I see.
It's the first ZEPP tour since I've been in my current position.
That's right. I'm glad.
I'm so happy.
I had done the ZEPP tour when I was making my major label debut, and I felt frustrated because I couldn't fill the venue to capacity,
So this time, I will do my best and go to see them live.
So I did my best this time and went to see them live.
I'm sorry about that.
I'm sorry.
Let me go gold.
Let me get it sold.
Sold.
And then we'll go to karaoke, and then we'll have dinner.
And eat dinner.
I wish I could.
I want to go. I want to go see them. ZEPP is really nice, isn't it? The venue is easy to see.
Yes, it is.
It really is.
It's my favorite live music club, too, so I'm really looking forward to it.
Good luck on the ZEPP tour.
I'll do my best.
Let's go out for dinner in between. See you.
I want to go. I'm looking forward to it.
I'm looking forward to it.
Yeah.
I'm really looking forward to it.
I'm really glad I told you.
Yes, thank you so much.
I noticed we didn't talk about your birthday at all.
You said something about common ground.
That's for sure.
Let's do it again.
Let's do it.
We have no choice but to do it again.
But we can't talk about work, you know, with each other,
I think we have a lot to talk about,
I'm sure we can talk about a lot of things.
Yes, that's true.
I'm kind of passionate about it.
Yes, I do get passionate.
I think we share the same passion that lies dormant around here, don't we? That's why.
That's what February 2nd has in common, isn't it?
Maybe.
Let's leave it at that.
What's the next anniversary?
It will be our 9th anniversary.
So, there will be some kind of concert on the 9th anniversary.
Yes, we combined the 9th anniversary with the 9th anniversary.
It's exactly 9 times 9, isn't it?
That's right.
So this year is our 9th anniversary,
Fukuoka Citizens Conference.
I've been to Fukuoka before.
I have strong memories of this place.
That's right. I think everyone in my hometown has been to this hall.
And I have always wanted to be there. I wanted to be on stage here,
It's a very hot place for me.
It's hot.
It looks like a hot opportunity, doesn't it?
It's so hot, lol.
That's why I'm going to do my best to get people to come.
That's why I'm going to start with the ZEPP tour,
I'm going to meet you all and tell you that Kyushu is good.
I will do my best to tell everyone that Kyushu is great and I would be happy if everyone could come to Kyushu.
Hot, hot, hot!
I'll make this year's goal of going out to eat come true somewhere, I promise.
I'll be watching you guys more than everyone else.
I'll eat it the rest of the time.
This video was sent to you by Nukumeshi, who eats his rice in the comfort of his own home.
The birthday present I want is to eat some delicious rice cakes in front of the results when I go to Fukuoka.
I'll sit across from you.
Please make sure that you have a seat in front of me.
The birthday present I want is to meet Saki again on February 4, and I want you to take a group shot of us.
I can take it anytime.
Please do this.